nxtbook.com 2012-12-21

# Nxtbook Media - Privacy Policy

privacy policy

Intellectual Property

The Nxtbook web site and nxtbooks contain copyrighted material, trademarks and other proprietary information including text, photos and graphics. Nxtbook owns, or has right to use, intellectual property rights in the entire Nxtbook experience, including the selection, coordination, arrangement and enhancement of the web site and the publications contained therein or delivered thereby, as well as in the content original to it. Each third-party content provider owns the copyright in content original to it including, without limitation, in the magazines and other publications delivered or otherwise made available to you by Nxtbook technology. You may not modify, publish, transmit, display, participate in the transfer or sale, create derivative works, or in any way exploit the content of the Nxtbook web site, the nxtbooks, or any portion of them. Except as otherwise expressly permitted under copyright law, you may not copy, redistribute, publish, display or commercially exploit any material from the Nxtbook web site or nxtbooks without the express permission of Nxtbook and the copyright owner. In the event of any permitted copying, redistribution or publication of material from the Nxtbook web site or nxtbooks, no changes in or deletion of author attribution, trademark, legend or copyright notice shall be made. Except as permitted by the Publication's lawful owner, you acknowledge that you do not acquire any ownership rights by reading, clipping or downloading copyrighted material. Except as permitted by Nxtbook or the copyright owner, nxtbooks are for your personal use only and may not be modified, reverse engineered, redistributed, sold, publicly displayed, licensed, rented or otherwise provided to a third party or commercially exploited. We do not grant you any licenses, express or implied, to the intellectual property of Nxtbook or our publishers except as expressly authorized by these terms.

Third-Party Content

Nxtbook is a digital publishing technology provider (and not a publisher) of nxtbooks or other content supplied by third parties. Accordingly, we have no editorial control over such content. Any opinions, advice, statements, services, offers or other information or content expressed or made available by third parties, including those made in nxtbooks offered by our web site, are those of the respective author(s) or publisher(s) and not of Nxtbook. Neither Nxtbook nor any third-party provider of information guarantees the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any content. Under no circumstances will we be liable for any loss or damage caused by your reliance on information obtained through a nxtbook. It is your own personal responsibility to evaluate the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any information or content available through a nxtbook.

A nxtbook may contain links to other Internet sites and third-party resources. Nxtbook does not assume any responsibility or liability for any communications or materials available at such linked sites. Nxtbook does not intend links in nxtbooks or on the Nxtbook web site to be referrals or endorsements of the linked entities; they are provided for convenience only.

Privacy

Please take a few minutes to read the following Policy. This Policy covers Nxtbook's treatment of information that we collect from you when you are on the Nxtbook web site and when you use our products and services. We do not collect personally identifiable information, which includes your name, mailing or billing address, email address, telephone number, or any other information that tells another person who you are. We may, however collect anonymous information that we will aggregate and use for general tracking and statistical purposes, or to determine whether your computer is compatible with our system.

Our policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Nxtbook does not own or control, or to individuals that Nxtbook does not employ or manage, including operators of web sites to or from which you may link from or to the Nxtbook web site or nxtbooks and the owners or managers of the magazines and other publications you read or otherwise access through nxtbook technology. If you have questions about our privacy policy, please e-mail us at [support@nxtbook.com](mailto:support@nxtbook.com).

What Information We Collect and Use

Nxtbook has the right to use and control the information collected on the Nxtbook web site and in nxtbooks. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this policy. Nxtbook collects information from users at different points on our web site and through nxtbooks, as follows:

Cookies

  * **What is a cookie?**  

    * A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. It can be used to provide you with a tailored user experience. 
  * **How does nxtbook use cookies?**  

    * Nxtbook may set and access our own cookies on your computer. Nxtbook uses cookies to facilitate the usage measurement of our web site and the distributed interactivity and measurement of nxtbooks. Nxtbook does not maintain any database of personally identifiable information that could be contained in cookies. 
  * **What information does Nxtbook put into user cookies?**  

    * When you visit our web site or open a nxtbook, we set cookies to identify you as a unique visitor, to maintain your session, and to test your browser and OS settings. 
  * **Do we retain the cookies?**
    * Nxtbook will retain cookies that are set by our web site or nxtbooks on your computer and will use them to recognize you when you return to the site or publication. 
  * **Third-party cookies?**  

    * Nxtbook may also allow other companies that are providing content, such as Publications, on our web site or in nxtbooks to set and access their own cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of cookies is subject to their own respective privacy policies. We do not have access to any information stored in cookies by third parties about you. 
  * **EU Law and Opting Out of Cookies**
    * In accordance with EU visitors, certain visitors must acknowledge and accept the use of cookies. You may delete and block all cookies from this site, but parts of the site will not work.

Internet Protocol Addresses

Your computer uses Internet Protocol or "IP" addresses every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer so that data (such as the web pages you request) can be sent to you. Our server automatically collects IP addresses. Nxtbook will not use your IP address to attempt to personally identify you.

Referrers

A "referrer" is the information passed along by a web browser that references the web URL you linked from, and is automatically collected by our web server. This information is collected and used by Nxtbook to understand the web sites referring traffic to our web site and to present appropriate content to our potential customers. Nxtbook tabulates referrer information on an aggregate basis to identify trends and traffic patterns. 

Nxtbook may enter into agreements with content partners that require nxtbook to count the number of product downloads stemming from a referral from a content partner site. This information is collected, used and aggregated by Nxtbook to fulfill the reporting requirements of those agreements. This information may also be combined with the referrer information described above and tabulated on an aggregate basis to identify general trends and traffic patterns.

Other

Nxtbook may automatically receive and record information in our server logs or from our cookie-based tracking service from your browser, including your IP address, your computer's name, the type and version of your web browser, referrer addresses and other generally accepted tracking information. We may also record web site page views (hit counts) and other general statistical and tracking information that is aggregated with that of other users in order to understand how our web site and nxtbooks are being used.
